

[Arif Gunawan]

Sukoharjo, Central Java, 57556 | +62 822 2972 0709

arifgunawan.professional@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/arif-gunawana46a71215/|https://github.com/aekgun/

## About me

I am Arif Gunawan, a graduate of Informatics Engineering STMIK Akakom Yogyakarta (UTDI). Having experience as Quality Assurance at PT. DBS Indonesia with responsibility for implementing UAT (User Acceptance Test) either manually or with automation tools. I have an interest in a career as a Quality Assurance Engineer and am able to create automation tools using the javascript language.

## **Ability & Competence**

- Microsoft Office
- JIRA
- Selenium

- Javascript
- SQL
- Robot Framework

## Work experience

PT. DBS (Jakarta, Indonesia)

Quality Assurance (March 2020 – March 2022)

- Responsible for conducting UAT (User Acceptance Test) starting from making Test Data, validating test results, to reporting bugs.
- Participate in the planning stage in determining the Test Case and Test Scenario to get an estimate of the clear test case and clear effort

Andre's Digital (Alor, Indonesia)

Graphic Design (December 2018 – January 2020)

• Contribute to building creative ideas and also be responsible for designing digital products

PT. Syncore (Yogyakarta, Indonesia)

Web Developer (June 2017 - October 2018)

Maintain and develop web-based application systems using PHP framework code igniter, plan application improvements, as well as test applications.

Hill Comp (Yogyakarta, Indonesia)

Hardware and network engineers (November 2010 – December 2011)

• Perform installation and configuration of operating systems, install computer networks, printers, and solve problems on computer networks.

## **Education**

STMIK Akakom Yogyakarta (UTDI)(2011-2016)

S1 Informatics Management - GPA 2.97

• Explore algorithms and data structures in various programming languages based on good, diligent and creative collaboration.

SMAN 1 Arosbaya (2012-2015)

Science major

• Participate in guiding the OSIS activities 2008 - 2009